theanimescrolls.com 2018-03-20

# Privacy Policy - TheAnimeScrolls

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which TheAnimeScrolls collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the http://www.theanimescrolls.com website (“Site”). Personal identification information  
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.  
Non-personal identification Information  
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users Whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.  
Web browser Cookies  
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.  
How we use collected information  
TheAnimeScrolls may collect and use users personal information for the following purposes:  
*.To run and operate our Site We may need your information display content on the Site correctly.  
*.To personalize user experience, We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.  
*.To improve our Site We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.  
*.To send periodic emails We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.  
How we protect your information  
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.  
Sharing your personal information  
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.  
Information Related to Advertising  
To support and enhance the Services, we may serve advertisements, and also allow third parties advertisements, through the Services. These advertisements are sometimes targeted and served to particular users and may come from third party companies called “ad networks.” Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms. We may engage with ad networks that are members or organizations or programs that manage the advertising privacy choices these ad networks offer consumers. To learn more about and adjust your preferences, please click here When you visit our Site or use our mobile applications or other Services, ad networks and other parties may collect information about your online activities overtime and across different websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these ad networks and other parties. Advertisements served through the Services may be targeted to users who fit a certain general profile category may be inferred from information provided to us by a user, may be based on the Services usage patterns of particular users, or may be based on your activity on Third Party Services. We do not provide Personal Information to any ad networks for use other than in connection with the Services.To increase the effectiveness of ad delivery,we may deliver a file (known as a “web beacon”) from an ad network to you through the Services. Web beacons allow ad networks to provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for us and for advertisers. Web beacons also enable ad networks to serve targeted advertisements to you when you visit other websites. Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network’s servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.  
Changes to this privacy policy  
TheAnimeScrolls has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.Your acceptance of these Terms by using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. This policy was generated using http://www.PrivacyPolicies.com Contacting us  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.
